

PROFILE

I am an experienced video editor, known for attention-to-detail, problem-solving and the ability to work independently to finish a project. I use technology and software to build and produce a finished product. I feel some of the skills I have gained through editing are transferable to a career in web development.

CONTACT

EVVVII.

dsanpedro@gmail.com

WEBSITE | WORK EXAMPLES https://dansanpedro.com/ https://github.com/Sanparty/

FAMILIAR WITH

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Vue.js

Agile

Git

TypeScript

WordPress

DAN SAN PEDRO

ASPIRING WEB DEVELOPER | VIDEO EDITOR

OBJECTIVE

I am exploring a transition to web development and eager to expand and improve upon my skills in this field. Having recently completed a reskilling program, I am looking to build upon that training and work towards securing a position in this high-technology area.

EDUCATION – WEB DEVELOPMENT

BELL U

January 2022 – September 2022

Web Application Developer Role Graduate Software Development Program

9-month intensive reskilling program focusing on

- Front End Web Development
- HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Vue.js JavaScript Framework
- Git & Version Control
- CI/CD Pipeline development

July 2022 – September 2022

On the Job Training - Internal Web Development Team – TSN.ca/RDS.ca

- making updates to existing Vue.js components, as requested by Product Owners
- Converting existing JavaScript code to TypeScript code as needed
- Using Gitlab and Sourcetree for version control

COURSERA

July 2022

Online Course Completed:

Create a Web Link Preview with VueJS Components

PLURALSIGHT

June 2022 – December 2022 Online Courses Completed Included:

Vue.js 3 Fundamentals Building Forms with Vue 3

ADVANCED

AVID Editing Software Adobe Photoshop Adobe After Effects Media Management Video Encoding

HOBBIES

Football (Soccer) Fan Watching Documentary Films Playing the piano and keyboard Playing tennis

CAREERFOUNDRY

August 2021 – September 2021 Online Course Completed: Intro to Front End Development

LINKEDIN LEARNING

July 2021 - September 2021 Online Courses Completed:

Succeeding in Web Development: Full Stack and Front End JavaScript Essential Learning

EDUCATION - BROADCASTING

RYERSON POLYTECHNIC UNIVERSITY

1994 - 1998 School of Radio and Television Arts Bachelor of Applied Arts Degree

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bell Media | EFP Editor

2014-Present

- Video editor for On-Air Promotions department
- Edit on AVID Media Composer Software
- Produce and online promos and image spots for various networks including HBO Canada
- Video encoding for social media, including YouTube, Facebook and Twitter
- Formatting videos in proper aspect ratio for Instagram/Twitter
- Utilizing various software, including Adobe Products:
 Photoshop, After Effects, Media Encoder and Illustrator

Astral Media | Online AVID Editor

2005-2014

- Video editor for On-Air Promotions department
- Interstitial Programming including interview segments, weekly entertainment show and lifestyle segments

TSN - The Sports Network Interactive | Web Editorial Assistant 1996-1998

- Designed and uploaded content to TSN Website, including video, news items, photos and feature items
- Updated real-time content, including live scoring and live chats
- Captured and encoded video for posting on website